Guide to the Collection of Aerial Photographs 1935-2001
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Aerial Photographs and Orthophotos, 1935-2000; Series II
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-06-05; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 20B 87-90
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-15; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 20C 1-21
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-06-05; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 21A 112-120
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-15; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 21B 1-21, 23
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-15; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 22B 1-23
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-06-05; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 23B 44, 46-47
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-15; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 23C 1-21
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-15; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 24C 8-21, 26-32
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-15; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 25 122-135, 139-145
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-09-08; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 26B 19-30
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-09-08; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 26C 1-15
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-15; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 27C 33-59
    Index photocopy map found in folder (1967?).
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-15; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 28 106-129
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-15; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 29 106-107, 109, 113-130
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 07-25-1976; 08-25-1976; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 30B 4-17
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-25; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 31C 83-84
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-25; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 31D 1-13
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-25; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 33B 80
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-25; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 34B 76-77
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-25; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 36B 92-101
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-25; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 37C 32-40
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-09-01; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 38B 16-25
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-08-31; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 39B 27
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-08-31; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 41C 46-48
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1978-08-05; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 41D 2, 11, 18
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-08-31; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 42A 68
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-09-01; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 42B 7-8
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-08-31; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 43 90-91
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-09-01; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 44D 13-15
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1978-08-05; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 44E 8
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1978-08-05; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 45B-20
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1978-08-05; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 46A-19
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1978-08-05; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 47A-14
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1978-08-05; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 48C-15, 21
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1978-08-05; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 50B-1, 7, 15, 19, 28
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1978-07-30; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 52A-12, 15, 19, 34, 35
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1978-07-30; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 53-3
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1978-07-30; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 54-1, 20
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1978-07-30; NW-C-76 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 59-10
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1984-07-18; NW-C-83 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2-64-234
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1984-07-18; NW-C-83 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2-65-197
  - Snohomish County, Washington (Southeast of Goldbar, Washington), 1984-07-18; NW-C-83 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2-74-137
  - Snohomish County, Washington (note on back), 1984-07-18; NW-C-83 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2-75-131, 132, 136
    T27N R9E (note on back)
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1983-05-23; NW-C-83 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 13-50-406, 407, 411, 412
  - Whatcom, Skagit, Snohomish Counties, Washington, 1983-07-18; NW-C-83 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 20-72-353
  - Whatcom, Skagit, Snohomish Counties, Washington, 1983-07-18; NW-C-83 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 20-82-201
  - Whatcom, Skagit, Snohomish Counties, Washington, 1983-07-29; NW-C-83 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 22-60-076, 077, 081, 084
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1983-07-29; NW-C-83 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 22-62-039, 041
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1983-07-29; NW-C-83 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 22-63-050, 051
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1983-08-04; NW-C-83 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 23-58-183
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1983-08-04; NW-C-83 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 23-59-264
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1983-09-19; NW-C-83 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 27-58-038, 039
  - Unidentified, 1983-09-12; NW-C-83 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 28-69-209
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1984-08-21; NW-C-83 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 29-67-121
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1960-1992 (Box 014)
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1969-06-16; NW-69 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 43-35C 10,15-17
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1969-06-16; NW-69 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 43-36C 14-19
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1985-03-15; C-BEL-85 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 6-2; 8-1; 9-4
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1979-07-18; 53073; United States. Dept. of Agriculture (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 179 - 60-67, 88-93, 106-112, 116-124
    Index available:
  - Kitsap and Mason County, Washington (Hood Canal Area), 1979-08-09; 626090; United States. Dept. of Agriculture (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 179-1 (Negative)
    Film Negative.
  - Whatcom County, Washington (Nooksack River Flood 1989), 1989-11-12; S89019 (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-1 thru 1-8; 2-1 thru 2-4; 3-1 thru 3-5
  - Whatcom, Skagit, San Juan Counties, Washington, 1990-07-10; NAPP (Box 014)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 215 photos
  - Asotin County, Washington - Clarkston into Garfield County, 1966-09-30; 5-128; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4-18 to 4-22; 5-23 to 5-25; 6-26 to 6-38
  - Garfield County, Washington -Snake River to Whitman County - Snake River west of Uniontown -, 1950-08-26; WHIT CCI-5G; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 53, 55, 57, 59
  - Whitman County, Washington - Colton to Wilma, 1950-09-22; WHIT CCI-8G; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 17,19,21,22
  - Spokane County, Washington to Snake River (Spokane County line with Idaho), 1950-08-16; WHIT CCI-1G; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4 to 60 (even #s only)
  - Whitman County, Washington - Snake River to Albion, WA, 1951-09-06; WHIT CCI-9G; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 193-209 (odd #s)
  - Whitman County, Washington - Colton to Albion East (Kamiak Butte), 1950-08-22; WHIT CCI-2G; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 117-139 (odd #s), 140
  - Whitman County, Washington - Colton to Pullman, 1950-08-16; WHIT CCI-1G; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 76-90 (even #s)
  - Whitman County, Washington - Uniontown to Palouse, 1950-08-22; WHIT CCI-2G; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 70, 71-99 (odd #s)
  - Whitman County, Washington - Palouse to Garfield, 1950-09-22; WHIT CCI-8G; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 64, 66, 68, 70
  - Whitman County, Washington - Pullman to Garfield, 1950-08-04; WHIT CCI-9G; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 143-161 (odd #s)
  - Whitman County, Washington - North Garfield to Spokane County Line, 1950-08-22; WHIT CCI-3G; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 36-50 (even #s)
  - Whitman County, Washington - Pullman to Spokane County Line, 1959-08-22; WHIT CCI-2G; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4-38 (even #s), 39
  - Whitman County, Washington - Garfield to Spokane County Line, 1950-08-22; WHIT CCI-2G; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 47-63 (odd #s)
  - Whitman County, Washington - East Pullman to Spokane County Line, 1950-08-22; WHIT CCI-3G; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3-27 (odd #s)
  - Whitman County, Washington - Colfax to Rosalia, 1939-07-21; WHIT CCI-240; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 33-60
  - Whitman County, Washington - North Colfax to North Steptoe, 1939-07-21; WHIT CCI-240; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 10-22
  - Whitman County, Washington - East Colfax to East Steptoe, 1939-07-21; WHIT CCI-240; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 85-94
  - Whitman County, Washington - South Fork Palouse River to Glenwood, 1939-07-21; WHIT CCI-241; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-6, 60-64, 92-96
  - Whitman County, Washington - Palouse Vicinity to West Palouse, 1939-07-21; WHIT CCI-242; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-5, 60-69
  - Whitman County, Washington - Winona to West Ewan, 1950-08-25; WHIT CCI-4G; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 74-82 (even #s)
  - Whitman County, Washington - West Winona to Pucket Creek, 1950-09-21; WHIT CCI-2G; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 245-251 (odd #s)
  - Whitman County, Washington - Palouse River to Ewan, 1950-08-28; WHIT CCI-7G; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 104-112 (even #s)
  - Whitman County, Washington - Endicott to North Lancaster, 1950-08-28; WHIT CCI-7G; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 015)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 65-73 (odd #s)
  - Pend Oreille County, Washington - South Usk to East Ruby, 1943-09-07; DDA-1B; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 49-60
  - Stevens County, Washington - North Springdale to North Valley, 1938-09-11; BBD-36; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 93-100
  - Stevens County, Washington - West Loon Lake to East Valley, 1938-09-11; BBD-37; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 15-24
  - Stevens County, Washington - Northeast Orin to Colville vicinity, 1938-09-11; BBD-35; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 45-48, 73-76
  - Stevens County, Washington - East Stevens vicinity to East Colville vicinity, 1943-09-01; BBD-1B,3B,4B,5B; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: See folder
  - Walla Walla County-Benton County, Washington - Lake Wallula to Snake River, 1940-09-01; CCH-4A; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-5, 18-24, 49-61, 76-81
  - Franklin County, Washington - Eltopia vicinity, 1955-07-19; AAU-3P; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 188-189
  - Franklin County, Washington - Mesa vicinity, 1955-07-19; AAU-3P; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 150-151, 180-181
  - Franklin County, Washington - Connell vicinity, 1955-07-19; AAU-3P; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 10-11
  - Franklin County, Washington - Kahlotus vicinity, 1955-07-19; AAU-1P; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 016)
  - Klickitat County, Washington - McCredie-Alderdale to Alder Creek, 1954-08-06; AAS-3N; AAS-4N; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Commodity Stabilization Service (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3N-148, 150, 151, 159-162; AAS-4N-8, 9, 10, 117, 118, 120
  - Klickitat County, Washington - Roosevelt north, 1954-08-04; AAS-1N; AAS-2N; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Commodity Stabilization Service (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1N-148, 149, 154; 2N-105-106
  - Grant County, Washington - Trinidad to Quincy East, 1956-07-16; B-6 10; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 5-1 thru 5-10
    Scale: 1:9,600
  - Douglas County, Washington - Columbia River to Northeast Rock Island, 1955-05-20; AAQ-1P; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Commodity Stabilization Service (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 132-139
  - Douglas County, Washington - South Rock Island to North Rock Island, 1955-05-20; AAQ-1P; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Commodity Stabilization Service (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 151-157
  - Douglas County, Washington - East Laurel Hill to North Malaga, 1955-05-20; AAQ-1P; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Commodity Stabilization Service (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 75-80
  - Douglas County, Washington - Laurel Hill to East Wenatchee, 1955-05-20; AAQ-1P; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Commodity Stabilization Service (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 19-24
  - Douglas County, Washington - West Malaga to North Wenatchee, 1956-07-16; B-6 10-1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-1 thru 1-8
  - Douglas County, Washington - East Rock Island to South Wenatchee, 1956-07-16; B-6 10-2; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2-1 thru 2-14
  - Douglas County, Washington - Northwest Trinidad to North Malaga, 1956-07-25; B-6 10-3; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Warren N. Hayner and Assoc. (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3-1 thru 3-12
  - Douglas County, Washington - West BArizonaColumbia River to East Rock Island Dam, 1956-07-25; B-6 10-4; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Warren N. Hayner and Assoc. (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4-1 thru 4-16
  - Douglas County, Washington - Wenatchee Heights to West Rocky Reach Dam, 1955-05-20; AAQ-1P; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Commodity Stabilization Service (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 5-13
  - Douglas County, Washington - Southeast Wenatchee Heights to East Wenatchee, 1955-05-20; AAQ-1P; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Commodity Stabilization Service (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 83-100
  - Douglas County, Washington - North Wenatchee to Entiat, 1955-05-20; AAQ-1P; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Commodity Stabilization Service (Box 016)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 31-39
  - Douglas County, Washington - Rocky Reach Dam to North Entiat, 1955-11-12; B-6 10-8; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 8-1 thru 8-18
  - Douglas County, Washington - Monitor to East Rocky Reach Dam, 1955-11-12; B-6 10-7; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 7-1 thru 7-9
  - Douglas County, Washington - Northwest Wenatchee to Rocky Reach Dam, 1955-08-29; B-6 10-6; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 6-1 thru 6-12
  - Chelan County, Washington - South Wenatchee to East Monitor, 1955-08-29; B-6 2-12; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 12-1 thru 12-10
  - Chelan County, Washington - West Monitor to Northeast Wenatchee, 1955-08-29; B-6 2-11; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 11-1 thru 11-10
  - Chelan County, Washington - South Wenatchee to Rocky Reach Dam, 1956-07-09; B-6 2-13; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 13-1 thru 13-20
  - Chelan County, Washington - Northwest Wenatchee to Corbaley Canyon, 1956-07-12; B-6 2-14; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 14-1 thru 14-19
  - Chelan County, Washington - Southwest Entiat to Cobaley Canyon, 1955-08-24; B-6 2-16; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 16-1 thru 16-9
  - Chelan County, Washington - North Rocky Reach Dam to North Entiat, 1956-08-09; B-6 2-15; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 15-1 thru 15-8
  - Chelan County, Washington - East Entiat to East Ardenvoir, 1955-11-12; B-6 10-9; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 9-1 thru 9-9
  - Chelan County, Washington - North Entiat to Columbia River, 1955-11-10; B-6 10-10; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 10-1 thru 10-7
  - Chelan County, Washington - Columbia River to East of Ardenvoir, 1955-11-12; B-6-10-11; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 11-1 thru 11-6
  - Chelan County, Washington - Columbia River to Lake Chelan, 1956-07-15; B-6 10-12; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 12-1 thru 12-11
  - Chelan County, Washington - Lake Chelan to North Chelan Falls, 1955-08-25; B-6 10-13; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 13-2 thru 13-14
  - Chelan County, Washington - Chelan Falls to West Azwell, 1956-07-31; B6 10-14; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Warren N. Hayner and Assoc. (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 14-1 thru 14-17
  - Douglas County, Washington - West Badger Mountain - North Entiat, 07-31-1956; 10-15-1955; B-6 10D-1, B-6 10D-2; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Warren N. Hayner and Assoc. (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 10D 1-1 thru 1-9; 10D 2-1 thru 2-4
  - Douglas County, Washington - East Entiat to Columbia River, 1955-10-15; B-6 10D-3; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3-1 thru 3-11
  - Douglas County, Washington - East Ardenvoir to Columbia River, 1955-10-15; B-6 10D-4; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4-1 thru 4-11
  - Chelan County, Washington - Columbia River to South Chelan Falls, 1956-07-22; B-6 10D-5; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Warren N. Hayner and Assoc. (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 5-1 thru5-14
  - Chelan County, Washington - South Chelan Falls to East Chelan, 1956-07-22; B-6 10D-6; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Warren N. Hayner and Assoc. (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 6-1 thru 6-13
  - Chelan County, Washington - Chelan Dam to Columbia River, 1955-10-15; B-6 10D-7; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Western Mapping Service (Box 017)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 7-1 thru 7-7
  - Chelan County, Washington - East Chelan Dam to Azwell, 1955-10-17; B-6 10D-8; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Warren N. Hayner and Assoc. (Box 018)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 8-1 thru 8-7
  - Chelan County, Washington - East Lake Chelan to Northwest Azwell, 1956-07-31; B-6 10D-9; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Warren N. Hayner and Assoc. (Box 018)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 9-1 thru 9-8
  - Klickitat County, Washington - White Salmon to Skamania County, 1954-08-04; AAS-1N; AAS-2N; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Commodity Stabilization Service (Box 018)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1N-90 thru 1N-92; 2N-32 thru 2N-33; 2N-90 thru 2N-92
  - King County, Washington - Kent to Tukwila; Des Moines to West Tukwila, 1956-04-10; 56 S5; KING 56 S6; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Pacific Aerial Photos (Box 018)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 5S-15, 17, 19; 6S-16, 17, 18, 19
  - King County, Snohomish County, Washington - Richmond Beach to West Snohomish River, 1941-06-11; S6 S 1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 018)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 112-120
    Scale: 1:34,600
  - King County, Snohomish County, Washington - Northwest Seattle to East Earlmont, 1941-06-11; S6 S 1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 018)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 130-137
  - King County, Snohomish County, Washington - Northwest Edmonds to Snohomish River, 1941-06-11; GS S 1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 018)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 145-150
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Possession Sound to West Roosevelt, 1941-06-11; GS S 1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 018)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 164-170
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Glendale to Three Lakes, 1941-06-11; GS S 1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 018)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 177-183
  - King County, Washington - Beverly Park to Kirkland, 1953-05-07; 2-A-6; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 018)
    Scale: Unidentified
  - King County, Washington - Beverly Park to Kirkland, 1953-05-07; 2-A-6; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 018)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2-1 thru 2-6
  - King County, Washington - North Bothell to Renton, 1957-04-16; A-27-1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Pacific Aerial Photos (Box 018)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-1 thru 1-21
  - King County, Washington - Beverly Park to Kirkland, 1953-05-07; 2-A-6; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 018)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3-1 thru 3-9
  - King County, Washington - Beverly Park to Kirkland, 1953-05-07; 2-A-6; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 018)
  - King County, Washington - Beverly Park to Kirkland, 1953-05-11; 2-A-6; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 018)
  - King County, Washington - North Bothell to Renton, 1957-04-08; A-27-2; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Pacific Aerial Photos (Box 018)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2-1 thru 2-21
  - King County, Washington - North Bothell to Renton, 1957-04-08; A-27-3; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Pacific Aerial Photos (Box 018)